{
    "subject": "resource/Eric_Voegelin",
    "predicate": "ontology/influencedBy",
    "object": "resource/Plato",
    "human_readable": "Eric Voegelin was influenced by Plato.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9169571995735168,
            "question": "Who influenced Eric Voegelin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7690039873123169,
            "question": "Which ancient Greek philosopher had an influence on Eric Voegelin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7631897926330566,
            "question": "How did Plato's ideas shape Eric Voegelin's philosophy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6633109450340271,
            "question": "Who are some key figures that influenced Eric Voegelin's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6580148935317993,
            "question": "What is the connection between Plato and Eric Voegelin's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6426175832748413,
            "question": "Name a prominent philosopher who impacted Eric Voegelin's thinking."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5776164531707764,
            "question": "Eric Voegelin drew inspiration from which historical figure?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4767128825187683,
            "question": "What philosophical tradition is Eric Voegelin associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38487479090690613,
            "question": "Eric Voegelin's philosophy is often linked to which ancient thinker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2839517295360565,
            "question": "What philosophical lineage does Eric Voegelin belong to?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eric Voegelin was influenced by Plato.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8747_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eric Voegelin's philosophy is often linked to which ancient thinker?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8747_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What philosophical tradition is Eric Voegelin associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8747_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eric Voegelin drew inspiration from which historical figure?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8747_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8747_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8747_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8747_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8747_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8747_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8747_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8747_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8747_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8747_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8747_69.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide several mentions of Eric Voegelin's engagement with Plato, including his interpretation of Plato's philosophy and his attempt to rearticulate Plato's effort millennia ago. This suggests that Voegelin was influenced by Plato."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provided discuss Bernat Torres's analysis of the philosophical influences on Eric Voegelin, with a significant emphasis on Voegelin\u2019s engagement and influence from Plato. The texts describe how Voegelin viewed Plato as both a teacher and model for his own philosophical endeavors, absorbed Aristotle\u2019s concept of nature into his political theory, and found in Plato\u2019s work foundational insights that shaped his approach to philosophy and politics. Therefore, the information supports the statement that Eric Voegelin was influenced by Plato."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}